Governor Iwatsu
岩津知事
Thanks for your speech today
非常感谢您今天拨空进行演讲
Not a big deal
哪里
If you have any more questions about regulations on presentation
只要是表现规制相关的演讲
contact me any time
随时都可以和我联络
Do you mind if
您觉得如何呢
we have a meal together in a while and discuss it further?
待会一起吃顿饭来深入探讨这项议题
The car is waiting for me    Thanks for you invatitation
车子已经在等我了  谢谢你的好意
Time to say goodbye
那么我先告辞了
Pardon me
不好意思
Please follow that car in the front
麻烦跟着前面那辆车
OK
好的
We're counting on you.
拜托你了
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode12   Battle! HXEROS
第十二话「决战！HXEROS」
That is to say
那也就是说
No Pets Allowed
禁止宠物入内
Whether she is a mimic Kisei Chuu at all
就只有茶茶有办法进行确认吗
can only be verified by Tya Tya
就是这么回事
That's true
就算是这样  但在光天化日下做确认
Even if that's the only way   verifying in the public
万一真的是规制虫的话就太危险了
would be too dangerous if she is
再说根本不会有人听我们的话吧
Also no one would listen to us as well
既然这样的话
If that's the case
我们干脆直接去找她吧
How about just confront her
有道理
That may work
怎么了  茶茶
What's wrong Tya Tya
烈人
Retto
我有帮上大家的忙吗
Am I being helpful to you all
HXEROS明明都已经消失了
HXEROS has disappeared already
大家却一样很关心我
But all of you still cares about me
还让我借住在家里
and allow me to stay in your home
但我现在都还没帮到任何忙
Yet I have not help anything
没有这种事
Don't say that
你现在不是正在努力想帮忙了吗
Aren't you trying right now
而且
And
多亏有茶茶我们才能做出战斗服
It was Tya Tya that makes it possible for us to make battle suits
我也很庆幸能遇见大家
I'm glad that I've met all of you as well
我的压岁钱…
My pocket money...
先跟你说  还有回程的车钱喔
Just a heads up  we would need a return trip as well
话又说回来
Anyway
为什么知事会住在这么偏僻的地方啊
Why would a governor live in such a remote place
确实有一点奇怪呢
True Strange a little bit
接下来该怎么办
What shall we do now
突然有一群高中生不请自来
A group of high schooler here with no plasible reason
不管怎么想都太可疑了吧
sounds so suspicious in any sense
要不要按完电铃就逃走
How about ring the bell then run
万一她真的是知事的那该怎么办
What if she is the real governer
那就由我去吧
Then let me do it
只要我一个人拟态和她接触
If I mimic myself and contact her
就不会被怀疑了
then we won’t be suspected
这  这样太危险了
That's too dangerous
对方说不定是敌人啊
She may be our enemy
怎么能让茶茶自己一个人去那种地方呢
How can we let Tya Tya go there alone
即使如此
Even if you say that
我还是想多帮大家一点忙
I still want to help
大家让一直孤单一人的我  有了自己的归宿
You guys give me a home for me I'm no longer alone
如果说还能再回到那个地方
The thinking of returning home
我感觉自己也能努力下去了
gives me a reason to make efforts
茶茶
Tya Tya
而且
Moreover
要是真的有个万一
even if something went wrong
我相信大家一定会来救我的
I belive that you guys will save me
是
Of course
我们说好了
We have a deal
听好了  茶茶
Listen Tya Tya
你的任务很简单
Your mission is simple
你只要进到那个知事家里
Get into the governer's house
确认一下有没有规制虫的痕迹就行了
and examine whether there's trace of Kisei Chuu
如果没问题的话  你直接回来就行了
If there's no problem    just come back directly
要是她是规制虫的话呢
What if she is Kisei Chuu
我们会一起过去救你
We would come together and save you
到时候你就拼命逃跑吧
Just keep running in that case
没问题  我一定能办到
No problem    I can do it
有…有您的包裹
You…You have a package
她真的不要紧吗
Is she okay?
她那个演技实在是有点…
Her acting is kind of…
好的
Yes
来了
This is she
有事吗
What is it
那就是知事吗
Is she the governer
与其说是知事  感觉比较像是痴女吧
I'd rather call her pervert than governer
请…请帮我签收
Sign…Sign this for me please
茶茶那家伙是怎么了
What happened to Tya Tya
她在做什么
What is she doing
白雪同学
Shirayuki
大家请先待在那里等我吧
Please wait me there
真是的
Oh My
你刚才不是才说很危险了吗
You know it's dangerous
奇怪  她们跑到哪去了
Strange Where did they go
我们擅自进来没关系吗
Is it okay for us to come in this way
反正门现在是开着的
The door is open anyway
而且我们是在找人  对方应该会原谅我们吧
And we are looking for someone It would excuse us
茶茶
Tya Tya
你终于回来了
You have come back
我可爱的宝贝女儿
My cute dear daughter
而且
And
你还为我准备了这么丰富的伴手礼
You've prepared a exquisite gift like this
我真开心
I'm delighted
来吧  我们一起去那边用餐吧
Come Let us have food together
这到底是怎么回事
What is this on earth
她刚才是不是称呼茶茶为自己的女儿
Did she just call Tya Tya her daughter
那也就是说
Namely
她是女王规制虫
She is the queen of Kisei Chuu
没想到我们这么快就见到面了
I did not expect to see you so soon
话又说回来  你们竟然…
Anyway You guys managed to…
让关在巢穴中的这个孩子逃了出来
Save my locked kid from the nest
快离开她  茶茶
Run Tya Tya
我要击倒那家伙
I'm gonna beat her
不要紧的
It's fine
我不会伤害你的朋友的  放心吧
I'm not going to hurt your friends Take it easy
我只是让他们没办法逃走而已
I would just keep them here
对了对了
By the way
这房间是以用H能源  绝对无法破坏的素材打造的
This room is build by Energe-H proof materials
你们想出去也是没用的
You would not find a way out
你们就留在这慢慢储存没用的H能源吧
Just stay here and save your Energe-H
果然还是打不开
Really It won't open
这边也是
Same this side
想不到茶茶她竟然会背叛我们
I can't believe Tya Tya betrayed us
怎么可能会有这种事呢
That's impossible
对不起  舞姬
Sorry Maihima
我也不是真心这么想的
I don’t mean to  say that
我才该要道歉
I'm the one who should appologize
只是…
But
茶茶的样子和平常不一样  让我感到很在意
Tya Tya looks different from usual    which gets my attention
总而言之
Anyway
得先想办法离开这里才行
We have to get out of here first
怎么样
How about it
这颗星球的料理也不错吧
The food of this planet taste good as well
话说回来那些人类全都吓了一大跳呢
Anyway Those humans get so scared
他们一定没料到
Surely they won't know
我拥有随心所欲操纵  所有规制虫的能力吧
I have the ability to control all Kisei Chuu
怎么了
What's wrong
你不吃吗
You are not eating
我不需要
I don’t have to
也对  你说的没有错
That’s true You are right
我们应该吃的不是这些东西
We should not eat these kind of things
不过  你不需要担心
Yet Don't worry
我会为你准备H能源的喂食场
I will prepare a feeding farm for you
就用那些人类
Using those humans
我已经注意到了
I have noticed
如果我们要将人类彻底灭绝
If we want to extinguish humans
就非得要走遍这整颗星球才行
We'll have to go all over this planet
所以说我要抓住几个  H能源量极高的人类加以隔离
So I need to catch a few humans with High Energe-H and take them in prison
并借此不断地获取H能源
to gain Energe-H continuously
将他们当成家畜饲养
Like riase livestock
这种事  我是不会让你得逞的
That kind of thing   I'm not going to let it happen
不行
No way
看来H能源真的无法打穿这个房间
It's true that Energe-H won't work on this room
可恶
Hell
而且这里偏偏是在收讯圈外
This place is out of the communication circle
难道我们已经无计可施了吗
Are we  runing out of ideas
不  我们还有一个办法
No  We still have one more
不过这是
Whatever it is
我们埼玉支部长久以来视为禁忌的方法
a way taken as a taboo of Saitama branch for a long time
要打破这禁忌得要有相应的觉悟才行
To be able to use it, you have to have a sense of consciousness.
难  难道要用那个方法
Are   Are you saying
不  绝对不能用那个方法
No  We can't use it
你在说什么啊  炎城
What are you saying Enjo
现在是紧急状况
It's emergent
既然现在只剩这个办法
If that's the only way
那我们也只能去做了吧
Then we have to do it
所以
So
你说的方法是什么
What is the idea you are talking about
那就是
That is
在成员彼此同意的前提下
On the premsie of mutal consent
做色色的事
Do some erotic things
你  你到底在说什么啊
What   What are you talking about
如果要打破这个墙壁
If we want to break the wall
就得使出超乎那些家伙  预料的力量才行啊
We have to wield more power than their expectation
白雪同学也帮我说说她啊
Shirayuki Please help me stop her
就这么办吧
That's the only way
因为我实在
Since I can't
不觉得茶茶会背叛我们
believe that Tya Tya is a turncoat
我想这一定是有什么隐情的
I think there must be a reason
为了确认事情的真相
To examine the truth
我们得快点离开这里
We'll have to leave here as soon as possible
不做色色的事就出不去的房间
A room that requires you to do erotic things
原来如此  值得参考
That's the matter  A good reference
怎么连小宙都这样啊
Even Sora are like this
而且你自己不是都说什么都愿意做了吗
Don't say you would do anything
是这样没错
It's true
怎么办
What should I do
再这样下去
If it goes this way
大家都会惨遭炎城的毒手的
Every one would be Enjo's victim
要是让小烈靠那种方法储存H能源
If we let Enjo get Energe-H using that way
我也会觉得很火大就是了
I'm gonna get vicious
所以呀
So
大家听我说
Everyone listen to me
我想这种事情
I think this kind of thing
还是应该和以心相许的对象去做
should only be done with your lover
我认为这样
In my view, this way
H能源也比较容易变得更强
would be easier to make Energe-H stronger
所以说
So
要在房间内一片漆黑  谁也无法认得彼此的状态下
In the dark room where none of us is recognizable
靠着各自的妄想力来储存H能源
and produce Energe-H using our own imagination
这就是我的条件
This is my condition
我有问题
I have a question
这样听起来
It sounds like
我该不会也得一起参…
I have to attend as…
云母现在好不容易有干劲了
Eventually Kirara gets motivated
你不要跑出来乱啦
Don’t mess it up
我是岩津藻贺奈  今年十七岁喔
My name is Iwazu Mokana 17 years old
难道说现在
Has it
已经开始了吗
started already
从这个胸部之大…
From the size of this boob…
应该说之小来判断
the small boob to judge
是桃园吗
is it Taoyuan
这个感觉
This kind of feeling
看来是中奖了
Looks like I'm getting lucky
等…
wait…
桃园这家伙到底在搞什么鬼啊
What the hell is Taoyuan doing
再这样下去就糟糕了
It wouldn't end well this way
烈人那家伙跑到哪去了
Where did Enjo go
抓到你了
Got you
摸起来怎么软软的
Why it feels so soft
根本就不是烈人啊
Not Enjo at all
不可以  千夜…
Don't   Chiya…
谁啊
Who
得救了
Finally
总之得先找件衣服来穿
Anyway I have to get dressed first
仔细凝视应该多少能看得清楚点吧
if I try carefully I should be able to see something
什么也看不见
Well Nothing
怎么回事
What happened
屁股那边好像有股暖暖的气息
There's a warm breath near my butt
既然视觉不管用  那换嗅觉的话呢
If eyes won’t work   how about nose
果然还是不行吗
Well still don’t work
看来也只能慢慢摸索了
Guess I have to grope
等一下
Wait a minute
可以别搔自己的腋下发出声音吗
can you stop touching your armpit and make noise
因为你都不肯好好储存H能源
Since you are not trying to get Energe-H
所以我才会示范给你看呀
I'm showing you how to do it
不用你多管闲事
It's none of your business
你又在说这种话了
Don't say that
难得的大餐摆在眼前
It's a good chance here
你想白白浪费掉吗
Are you going to waste it
你再不行动小烈说不定  会去找其他女生搅和喔
If you are not moving   Perhaps Enjo would go find other girls
我其实也很想…
In fact I also want to…
没问题
No problem
黑漆漆的没人会知道的
No one would see through darkness
稍微来一下应该…
a little bit won't..
这个触感  难道是…
This feeling   is it…
炎城
Enjo
星乃
Hoshino
这到底是怎么搞的啊
What the hell is happening
我们可能是掉进床的缝隙了
I think we fell into the gap between beds
你先别说了  快点走开啦
Don’t keep saying   just move right now
我也很想这么做
That's what I'm trying to do
可是手压在下面抽不出来
But my hands are pressed by you
可以先稍微把腰向上挺吗
can you move your waist first
不行
I can't
刚才因为黑云母的关系
Because of Black Kirara
现在变得很敏感
I'm being so sensitive right now
星乃
Hoshino
对不起  我的腰刚才没力
Sorry I was exhausted
我现在把腰挺起来
I'm moving my waist now
要慢慢来喔
Do it slowly
眼睛开始渐渐习惯黑暗了
My eyes is getting used to the darkness
星乃这家伙
Hoshino
可以了  抽出来吧
Done Pull it out
她怎么露出这种表情啊
Why she is having a face like this
看到她这种表情  我…
Seeing her like this    I…
想不到你竟然会反抗我这个女王
I can't believe you are against your queen
看来还是应该像以前那样  将你关起来比较好吗
Should I lock you up again like before
我已经不会再受你控制了
I'm no longer subject to your command
这么一说你是个突变异种呢
In this case, you are a mutant
现在我还可以原谅你
Still, I may forgive you by now
你究竟想选择哪边当同伴呢
Yet which side are you gonna pick
我的确不是规制虫  更不是人类
I am not Kisei Chuu   nor human
不过有件事我可以断言
But there's one thing I can confirm
我是HXEROS
I am HXEROS
是吗  真遗憾
Is it so    Pity
HXE  RED！
HXE  RED！
HXE  YELLOW！
HXE  YELLOW！
HXE  PINK！
HXE  PINK！
HXE  WHITE！
HXE  WHITE！
HXE  BLUE！
HXE  BLUE！
弩级战队HXEROS
SUPER HXEROS
各位
Everyone
对不起
Sorry
我也不晓得自己为什么会变成这样
I don't know why I did that
太好了  是平常的茶茶
Great It's the right Tya Tya
已经没事了  这里有我们在
It's fine now   We are here
亏我为你们选择了温柔的方法
Though I picked a soft way for you
看来有必要稍微惩罚你们一下了
I would not refuse to punish you a littlt bit
这是我们要说的话
That's what we are going to say
「天空的光翼」
Solar Ray
一击恼杀「松叶崩」！
A bow annoying kill   The Matsuba Hit
你觉悟吧  母后
Keep it real Mother
原来如此
That's the reason
难怪你们能破坏  抗H能源素材打造的房间
why you can break the room made of  Energe-H proof materials
原本念在你们是优秀的H能源  所以才放过你们
I did let you live for the sake of being good Energe-H resources
不过看来是没办法这样了
Yet it seems I was wrong
既然如此
So be it
这是什么声音
What is that sound
这孩子据说
This kid is said to be
是我们的祖先过去创造的生物兵器
A biological weapon made by our ancestors
为牠提供过量的H能源  结果就长得这么大了
Provide it with a glut of Energe-H     and it just get so huge
去吧  将他们收拾掉
Go    Take them down
不会吧
No way
这是什么啊
What is this
大家都没事吧
Is everyone ok
可恶  这家伙是怎么回事
Hell  On what earth is this
那孩子好像已经对H能源成瘾了
That kid seems already get addicted to Energe-H
要是让牠到街上恐怕  会演变成大灾难吧
If you let it go to the street   it would be a catastrophe
你们就好好加油吧
Try your best
你们两个快追上去
Go and get her
可是
But
我们这边会自己想办法的
We'll figure it out ourselves
没问题的  刚才的H能源还有剩
No problem    We still have Energe-H left
我知道了
Ok  I will go
我们待会一定会再回来的
We will come back soon
「脉冲回音砲」
Pulsating Echo Gun
你的对手是我们才对
Your match is us
奇怪  没有用？
Strange It didn’t work
为什么
Why
XERO  GEAR没有反应
XERO GEAR has no reaction
难道这家伙现在在吸收H能源吗
Is it absorbing our Energe-H right now
这种感觉和之前对付的海参一样
It feels like the trepang we fighted before
而且
And
和刚才那个女王说的一样
Just like the queen said
牠只要吸收H能源就会变得越来越大
It gets larger after getting more Energe-H
面对这种敌人我真的无能为力
I can't do anything against this kind of enemy
不过只要大家一起合作…
But as long as all of us cooperate…
各位  不可以输给这种家伙
Everyone Don’t give it up
怎么回事  身体好热
What happened  I feel so hot
感觉从身体内侧涌出了无限的H能源
It feels I'm getting infinite Energe-H
而且
And
感觉好舒服
It feels good
HXEROS「肉食状态」
HXEROS Erotic State
刚才那是怎么回事
What happened just now
没想到H能源竟然强大到  连XERO战斗服都无法承受
I can't believe Energe-H could be so powerful that even XERO battle suit can not hold it
拜托你们了
Counting on you
炎城同学  星乃同学
Enjo    Hoshino
星乃
Hoshino
那个…刚才很抱歉
I'm sorry for
对你做了那种事
doing that kind of thing to you
就是说啊
Right
我看你从床上滚下来也是故意的吧
I guess dropping from bed is on purpose as well
所以我不是都道过歉了吗
That' s why I appologize
而且我们两个还不是都有感觉
And both of us had feelings
这种事你好歹也讲得婉转一点吧
Don't be so straightforward on these kind of things
抱歉…
Sorry
真让我惊讶
It surprises me
想不到你竟然会一个人独自行动
that you act alone
你刚才做了什么
What have you done
我的能力呢
My power
是随心所欲操纵所有的规制虫
is to controll all the Kisei Chuu at my will
不过呢  给予过血液的生物也不例外
as well as those who accecpted my blood
这是什么意思
What does it mean
奇怪  身体动不了
Strange I can't control my body
你没事吧  星乃
Are you okay Hoshino
星乃
Hoshino
你在做什么啊  黑云母
What are you doing    Black Kirara
而且我怎么会被控制住啊
And why I am being controlled
这样正好
That will work
反正你们也消灭了我不少的同胞
You have killed many siblings of mine
得接收那些新鲜而强力的H能源
I have to get these new and powerful Energe-H
再多产一些卵才行
and lay more eggs
好难受…
I don’t feel well…
看来你果然没办法反抗
Looks like you cannot resist
人类的本性终究也不过如此
Is this the limit of human nature
怎么样
What do you say now
现在想当我的家畜了吗
Wanna be my livestock now?
难道没有什么办法  能让这家伙恢复原状吗
Is there any way to make her normal
再这样下去真的要…
keep it like this and I will…
快点想想
Think carefully
我不是一直都和她在一起吗
I've been always with her
星乃的弱点是…
The weakness of Hoshino is…
不行…这样不行啊
No…we can't do that.
这样子根本完全感受不到H能源啊
I can't sense Energe-H this way
星乃的优点
The merit of Hoshino
就是完全没注意到自己魅力的这点啊
is that she never take her charming advantage
炎城  你在说什么
Enjo What are you saying
原本以为个性强势又固执
I thought I hate her strong and stubborn character
却对强硬作风没辄
Yet I found I cannot resist her style
个性明明正经八百
As a serious girl
却还是一边抱怨一边决定加入HXEROS
she still decide to join HXEROS even with complains
满脸通红的害羞表情也很不错
It's good to see her blushes
不过
And
正因为她是这样的人
since she is this kind of person
偶尔露出的笑容才显得灿烂啊
That makes her simile more splendid
所以说我
So as of me
比起以前
comparing to the past
还是现在的星乃  更让我喜…
I'd love the current Hoshino more…
都这种时候了
At a time like this
你到底在说什么啊  笨蛋
What the hell are you saying  Asshole
终于恢复了
Finally You come back
你果然还是该像这样才对
This is your style
你的作法太粗暴了啦
You are being too rude
我们上吧  星乃
Let's do it Hoshino
靠我们一起打倒那家伙
Defeat her by our force
区区的家畜
Trivial livestock
竟敢妨碍我用餐
How dare you hamper my lunch
我要用这招了结你们
I will end you with this
这个感觉  我回想起来了
This feeling   I have recalled
第一天战斗时的事
The first day in the battle
我从来没有
I've never
感受过这么惊人的H能源
seen so amazing Energe-H
太迷人了
Tempting
两股H能源相辅相成发出的
The synergy of two Energe-H produces
结合H能源竟然会如此美味
compounding Energe-H    and it is so tasty
这就是我们梦寐以求的H能源…
This is the kind of H energy we've dreamed of…
这样一来我们的战斗就结束了吧
Is this the end of our battle
肯定是这样
It must be
所以说星乃
So Hoshino
之前的约定现在还有效吗
Is your promise still vaild
你说过击败所有规制虫后
You've said after defeating all the Kisei Chuu
你就会答复我对你的告白
You will give me a response
到时候我会给你答复的
I will answer you at that time
都这种时候了你还在说什么啊
Why are you asking at a time like this
什么叫都这种时候啊
What is a time like this
我之所以能一路撑到现在
The only reason for me to hold out till now
就是因为有这个心灵支柱啊
is  the spiritual support like this
现在各地都还有剩下的规制虫吧
There still are many Kisei Chuu left in other places
等清除掉她们再说吧
Let's talk after taking them down
这次就先这样吧
So be it
你干嘛笑咪咪的啦
Why are you laughing
因为一想到还能再稍微看到  星乃害羞的模样一阵子
Because as long as I can see you blushes
就感觉好像也不坏
It feels fine
我不要再当英雄了啦
I don’t want to be heroe any more
几天后
Several days later
原本还在想到底会怎么样呢
I was think what would happen
我的嫌疑终于洗清
My fame has finally been cleared
HXEROS也顺利重新集结了
HXEROS has managed to assemble again
今后要再拜托你们了
I'm still going to expecting you in the future
还得改良XERO战斗服才行呢
to improve XERO battle suits
我也来一起帮忙吧
I'll help
万事拜托了
Counting on you
怎么了怎么了
What What
你的H能源用光了吗
Did you use up your Energe-H
来吧
Come
等一下
Wait a minute
百花  不要这样啦
Don’t do this Momoka
她们又开始了